Mangesh Nidhonkar (1) Featured

Assistant Technical Analyst seeking roles in Software Development, System Integration, Requirement Gathering, Visual force, Sales force, Technical Support, NetSuite, HTML, Apex, Force.com, Javascript, CSS, Core Java, C, Data Loader, Oracle, Workato, oops, SQL



Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 2 Month(s) Current Designation: Assistant Technical Analyst

Current Company: RevGurus Inc Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: PG Diploma [Internet of Things]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Mumbai, Pune Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Assistant Technical Analyst, Software Developer, Software Development, System Integration, Requirement Gathering, Visualforce, Salesforce, Technical Support, NetSuite, HTML, Apex, Force.com, Javascript, CSS, Core Java, C, Data

Loader, Oracle, Workato, oops, SQL

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

2+ years of experience as a administrator and Developer in Salesforce.com and NetSuite. Has good knowledge of the Technical and Functional aspects.

Certified - Salesforce Platform Developer 1

Customizing the applications on Salesforce platform and Force.com

Having good knowledge with Salesforce Apex, Visualforce programming, Lightning Web component, triggers and customizing salesforce standard functionality.

Having good knowledge of SFDX and Salesforce cli.

Having knowledge of system integration using REST services or using Workato as a middle ware tool.

Ability to learn and adapt to new technologies guickly.

Work Experience

RevGurus Inc as Assistant Technical Analyst

Mar 2019 to Till Date

Worked on the Salesforce developing Triggers, Apex classes and VF pages, designing of custom objects, custom fields, role based page layouts, custom Tabs, custom reports, Dashboard and various other components as per the client and application requirement.

Also worked on system integration using REST services and using Workato as a middle ware tool.

VM Infomatics as Software Developer Sep 2018 to Feb 2019

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Pune University in 2017

PG: PG Diploma (Internet of Things) from Center for development of advanced computing in 2018

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Salesforce Platform Developer 1

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Apex, Core Java, Python, C,			0 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Netsuite, SuiteScript, SuiteTalk		0	0 Year(s) 5 Month(s)
Visual Force, Apex Triggers, Data loader			1 Year(s) 8 Month(s)
JavaScript, HTML			
MY ECLIPSE, Eclipse			
MySQL, SOQL, SOSL			0 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Windows, Linux (Ubuntu)			
Internet of Things (IoT), MQTT, HTTP			0 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
CoAP, Raspberry Pi			0 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Salesforce, Wokato		0	1 Year(s) 9 Month(s)

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				

Projects

Project Title: IoT Based Farm Automation

Client: Centre For Development Of Advanced Computing

Duration: Jun 2018 - Jul 2018 Nature of Employment: Full Time Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Project Details: We are using DHT22, Gas MQ-2, soil moisture sensors which is connected to the Raspberry Pi and we are using Think Speak Cloud. All operation are based on API key. user send all data from Raspberry Pi to cloud with the help of

Project Title: Smart Traffic Monitoring Using Naive Bayes Algorithm

Client: NA

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Aug 2016 - Jun 2017 Role: Programmer Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Team Size: 4

Skill Used: Android, Java programing, SQL

Role Description: My role is create android application for user and for admin.

so I have created 2 android application.

Project Details: NA

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent 1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=bf56d08bff6fdba33389f495985e7dbe09085a544c1501140715465f5a5d...

Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time